PR 59 adds auto-discovery flags to lxa
board scan. Let's see them in action.
The --user and --org flags auto-discover
repos without manual configuration.
Let's create a new project board.
The board is created with workflow columns
ready.
Now the magic: scan with --user to
auto-discover all repos with activity.
Without specifying any repositories, it
found and added items automatically.
PR 59 also adds Gist-based config sync for
ephemeral environments.
Config persists across sessions via GitHub
Gist.
Let's view the board on GitHub to see our
auto-discovered items.
Here's our board in kanban view. On the
left we see Icebox and Backlog columns
with open issues.
Scrolling right we see Agent Coding and
Human Review columns for items needing
attention.
And here are Final Review, Approved, Done,
and Closed columns tracking the full
workflow.
Each item was auto-discovered and placed
based on its GitHub state.